Stanford University, Office of Student Activities, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of Student Activities and Leadership, records
1943-2014
SC0368
Stanford University. Dean of Student Affairs.
Stanford University. Office of Student Activities and Leadership.
Stanford University. Office of Student Activities.
40 Linear feet
Correspondence, memos, minutes, reports, lists, guidelines, policies, printed materials, registrations, constitutions, and other records pertaining to the administration of student organizations on campus and support services provided by the Office of Student Activities and Leadership (and its predecessors, the Office of Student Activities, and Student Organization Services ) including space allocation, funding, custodial services, maintenance, and leadership retreats. Collection also includes information files on fraternities and sororities, 1943-2003.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Materials were transferred from the Office of Student Activities and Leadership, and its predecessor the Office of Student Activities, from 1989 through 2014.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Office of Student Activities and Leadership, under the jurisdiction of the Office of Student Affairs, provides information and assistance to students on organizing their groups and activities. Previously known as the Office of Student Activities, under the jurisdiction of the Campus Affairs Office. Previous to November 1990, it was known as Student Organization Services.
Description of the Collection
Correspondence, memos, minutes, reports, lists, guidelines, policies, printed materials, registrations, constitutions, and other records pertaining to the administration of student organizations on campus and support services provided by the Office of Student Activities and Leadership (and its predecessors, the Office of Student Activities, and Student Organization Services ) including space allocation, funding, custodial services, maintenance, and leadership retreats. Collection also includes information files on fraternities and sororities, 1943-2003.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Dean of Student Affairs.; Stanford University. Office of Student Activities and Leadership.; Stanford University. Office of Student Activities.; Stanford University. Student Organization Services.; Greek letter societies.; Student activities.
Collection Contents
- Original accession, Accession ARCH-1984-060
  - First Blyth Fund (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Second Blyth Fund (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Third Blyth Fund (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fourth Blyth Fund (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fifth Blyth Fund (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Blyth Fund, Papers and Balance Sheets (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Blyth Fund, Finances (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blyth Fund, Incoming Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Blyth Fund, Paper Clippings (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Blyth Fund, Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Blyth Fund, Agendas (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Blyth Fund, Advisors (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Blyth Fund, Investment Information (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Blyth Fund, Bio Response (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Blyth Fund, Bonds (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Blyth Fund, Broker Selection (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Blyth Fund, Broker, Belford Hammerbeck (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Blyth Fund, Broker, E.F. Hutton (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Blyth Fund, Cal Tech Stock Letter (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Blyth Fund, Citicorp (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Blyth Fund, Cash Reserve (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Blyth Fund, Convergent (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Blyth Fund, Corporate Information (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Blyth Fund, Graphic Scanning (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Blyth Fund, Groups (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Blyth Fund, Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Blyth Fund, Dow Jones (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Blyth Fund, Directors (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Blyth Fund, Donors (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Blyth Fund, Eastern Utilities (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Blyth Fund, Exxon (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Blyth Fund, First Alabama (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Blyth Fund, Balance Sheet and Assets (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Blyth Fund, Foreign Markets (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Blyth Fund, Investor's Responsibility (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Blyth Fund, Investor's Responsibility (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Blyth Fund, Japan Fund (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blyth Fund, Market Analysis (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Blyth Fund, Market Letters (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Blyth Fund, Market Letters (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Blyth Fund, Market Letters (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Blyth Fund, Mutual Funds (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Blyth Fund, Mutual Funds (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Blyth Fund, Old Proposals (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Blyth Fund, Options (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blyth Fund, OSA Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Blyth Fund, Occidental College (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Blyth Fund, Pan Am (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Blyth Fund, Portfolio Analysis (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blyth Fund, Provisions (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Blyth Fund, Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Blyth Fund, Questionnaires (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Blyth Fund, Reserve Fund (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Blyth Fund, Silverado Mines (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Blyth Fund, Sears (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Blyth Fund, Subaru (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Blyth Fund, Walter Heller (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Blyth Fund, US Antinomy Corp. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Blyth Fund, US Steel (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Blyth Fund, Zila Pharmacy (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Blyth Fund, Stock Information (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Environmental Education, Papers (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Environmental Education, Papers (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Environmental Education, Papers (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Environmental Education, Papers (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Environmental Education Bible (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University Security Portfolio, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Stanford in Government [SIG], Annual Report (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford in Government [SIG], Annual Report (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - SIG, Papers (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - SIG, Financial Aid (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - SIG, Credit Possibilities (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SIG, Interviews, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - SIG, Financial Aid, 1975-76 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - SIG, Reports and Lists (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - SIG, Calendar, 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - SIG, Agency Positions (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - SIG, Federal Agencies, Summer 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - SIG, Federal Agencies (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - SIG, Chairman's File, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - SIG, 1964-65 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - SIG, 1965-66 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - SIG, 1966-67 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - SIG, Newsletters (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SIG, Lobbying, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SIG, Brochure (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SIG, Sacramento (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SIG, Cities, 1972-73 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - SIG, Santa Clara County, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - SIG, Los Angeles (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SIG, Los Angeles (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - SIG, Sacramento 1969-70 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - SIG, Lobbying Reports (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - SIG, Lobbying Reports (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SIG, Papers, ca. 1976-77 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - SIG, Washington Interns, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - SIG, Fund Raising (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Blyth Fund, Address Catalogue (Box 7)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-1989-059
  Student Organization Services (SOS) was a division of the Campus Affairs Office, which was one of the administrative offices of the Dean of Student Affairs. SOS was responsible for authorizing all student organizations at Stanford, articulating and implementing relevant University policies, and providing services to student organizations.
  These records pertain to the administration of student organizations and services provided to them by the Student Organization Services including space allocation, funding, custodial services, maintenance, and leadership retreats. Included are correspondence, memos, minutes, reports, lists, guidelines, policies, and printed materials.
  - Space-General Information 1980-81 (Box 1)
  - 1980-81 VSO Space Allocations (Box 1)
  - Space Allocation 1982-83 (Box 1)
  - Space Allocation 1987-88 (Box 1)
  - Space Allocations Committee (Box 1)
  - 1986-87 Space Allocations Committee (Box 1)
  - Space: General (Box 1)
  - Space-General Information (Box 1)
  - El Centro 1983-84 (Box 1)
  - Old Firehouse Building (Box 1)
  - Space Allocations Committee Report (Box 1)
  - Women's Center (Box 1)
  - Task Force on Student Office Space 1983-84 (Box 1)
  - Space Inventory Reports (1983) (Box 1)
  - Annual Space Inventory Update 1983 (Box 1)
  - Boathouse 1984-85 (Box 1)
  - 1986/7 WO Printouts out bldgs (Box 1)
  - Documentation on 1986-87 Building Maintenance Budget (Box 1)
  - Juan Space Meetings 1987 (Box 1)
  - Task Outline (Originals) (Box 1)
  - Space Stanford AIDS Education Project 1986-87 (Box 1)
  - Misc. Space (Box 1)
  - Operations and Maintenance Paint Program (Box 1)
  - Knoll Annex (Box 1)
  - El Centro (Box 1)
  - KZSU (Box 1)
  - Black Community Services Center (Box 1)
  - Old Firehouse Maintenance (Box 1)
  - Organizational Analysis of OSA, Winter 1979 (Box 1)
  - SOS Overview (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1983 Sep (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1983 Oct (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1983 Nov (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1983 Dec (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Jan (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Feb (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Mar (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Apr (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 May (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Jun (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Jul (Box 1)
  - SOS Chron, 1984 Sep (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Oct (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Nov (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1984 Dec (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1985 Jan (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1985 Feb (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1985 Mar (Box 1)
  - OSA Chron, 1985 Apr (Box 1)
  - SOS Chron, 1985 May (Box 2)
  - SOS Chron, 1985 Jun (Box 2)
  - SOS Chron, 1985 Jul (Box 2)
  - VSO General Guidelines 1977 (Box 2)
  - Original Forms (Box 2)
  - SOS Original Correspondence 1985-86 (Box 2)
  - SOS Original Handouts 1985-86 (Box 2)
  - VSO General 1977-78 (Box 2)
  - VO Complaints (Box 2)
  - VO Inquiries (Box 2)
  - Funding (Box 2)
  - ASSU Program Board Funding (Box 2)
  - Brown Bag Lunches 1984 (Box 2)
  - SOS 1986-87 Information Sessions (Box 2)
  - OSA "Program Planning Workshop" (Box 2)
  - Student Directory 1986-87 (Box 2)
  - Student Directory 1987-88 (Box 2)
  - 1985 Convergence (Box 2)
  - Stanford Student Leadership Conferences (Box 2)
  - 1984 Synchronicity Evaluation (Box 2)
  - VSO List 1973-78 (Box 2)
  - VSO List 1978-79 (Box 2)
  - VSO List 1979-80 (Box 2)
  - Leadership Retreat (Box 2)
  - Retreat 1982-83 (Box 2)
  - L.R. for Permanent Records (Box 2)
  - Leadership Retreat 1983 (Box 2)
  - Political Guidelines Hassles 1984-85 (Box 2)
  - Clubhouse (Box 2)
  - Glee Club 1980-81 (Box 2)
  - Graduate Students (Box 2)
  - ASSU Fund Raising Benefit Drives (Box 2)
  - The Company (Box 2)
  - DOSA/OSA Celebration of Transition 82 Inaugural (Box 2)
  - ASSU Constitutional Amendments 1981-82 (Box 2)
  - ASSU-Treasurer's Orientation (Box 2)
  - Clubhouse 1972-83 (Box 2)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-1994-014
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha, 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Phi, 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Delta Delta Delta, 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Delta Gamma, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Delta Tau Delta, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Delta Upsilon, 1979-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Gamma Phi Beta, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Kappa Alpha, 1980 -1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1983-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1979-1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Kappa Sigma, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Omega Psi Phi, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Phi Delta Theta, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Phi Kappa Psi, 1977-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pi Beta Phi, 1984-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sigma Chi, 1980-1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sigma Delta Tau, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Theta Delta Chi, 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Theta Xi, 1980-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Zeta Psi, 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - IFC/ISC, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Survey of Frat & Soro. Presidents, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Survey of Frat & Soro. Presidents (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sorority Funds held in Trust (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sorority Funds held in Trust (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sororities: Background (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2008-235
  - The Bridge, reports to Advisory Board, 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Bridge reports to Advisory Board, 1991-93 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Bridge Live-ins and Space Allocation, Feb. 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Bridge: Application for an Applied Psychology and Health Theme House at Stanford University, Feb. 28, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Bridge, space issues, 1987-89 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chaparral historical info, 1968-69 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chaparral historical info, 1943-67 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chaparral space issue 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chaparral space issue--reference material (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chaparral space issue 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chaparral space issue 1975-94 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Flying Club, activity board, 1956-93 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Flying Club brochure (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Flying Club, problems, 1991-2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - KZSU 1973-87 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - SOCA (Student Organizing Committee for the Arts) 2001, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - SPOON Project 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Review--historical information 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Review--complaint correspondence 1989-95 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - thinkBIG Conference on International Women's Health and Human Rights, Feb. 2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Women's Needs Assessment Report Fall 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alcohol and Drug Use at Stanford (Training Materials for Stanford Residence Staff) 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Clippings on student life (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Housing Agreement booklets (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Inner Quad, requests for use of, 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Party Planning Guide, 1999-2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Student Giving, Policy Statement 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dean of Students Office--annual reports, 1996-98 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Students Office--annual reports, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Fraternal affairs--history, general, 1988-93 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fraternities, clippings, 1995-98 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fraternities, miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fraternity parties, flyer and clipping, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Greek System Status Report 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council correspondence, 1967-85 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - IFC Journal, April 19, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Alpha Delta Phi, 1984-85 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Delta Gamma 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon 1989-94 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Delta Tau Delta 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Kappa Alpha 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Phi Kappa Psi "the Great Joy of Serving Others" circa 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sigma Chi, Reunion 2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Zeta Psi 1981-84 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Additional material, 1972-2008; Accession ARCH-2010-121
  - Photocopies of Rush books, 1976-1989 (Box 1)
  - Interfraternity and Intersorority Councils Rush prospectus, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Greek Guide, 1992-1995 (Box 1)
  - Pledge Symposium, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Interfraternity Council Rush Prospectus, 1993-1997 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Greek Prospectus, 1998-200 (Box 1)
  - Rush/Recruitment, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Fraternity Prospectus Rush, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Fraternity Prospectus Recruitment, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Interfraterntiy Council Rush Prospectus, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Sorority Rush Book, 1993 (Box 1)
  - ISC [Inter-Sorority Council] Rush, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Sorority Rush, 1995-1997 (Box 1)
  - Sorority Prospectus, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Assorted Greek booklets and brochures (Box 2)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha sorority, 1980-2005 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Kappa Delta Phi records, 1993-2000 (Box 2)
  - Beta Theta Pi constitution and laws, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Chi Omega constitution and miscellany (Box 2)
  - Delta Delta Delta Annual Report, 1998-99 (Box 2)
  - Delta Sigma Theta sorority, 1980-1990 (Box 2)
  - Pi Beta Phi Policies and Standing Rules and other records, 1979-1990 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Theta Psi constitution (Box 2)
  - ASSU Constitution Amendment, 1993-1997 (Box 2)
  - Social Event and Party Planning Guides, 1993-2005 (Box 2)
  - OSA information cards (Box 2)
  - Student Organization Handbook [missing 1994, 1996, 2001, 2004], 1990-2007 (Box 2)
  - Student Organization Sourcebook, 1986-1989 (Box 2)
  - Student-Athlete Handbook, 2003 (Box 2)
- Additional material, 1978-2004; Accession ARCH.2014-052
  - Volunteer student organization files, 1978-2004
    - Active
      - African and Afro Ameri. Studies Majors and Minors Assoc., 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Aguila Real A.C., 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Aiki Weapons Club, 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Akwaaba, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Alaska Native Student Association, 1989-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Alliance Streetdance, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Alpha Phi Omega, 1979-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Alternative Spring Break, 1992-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Adventist Christian Fellowship, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Amateur Baseball Club, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - American Indian Science and Engineering Society, 1984-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - American Medical Association/ California Medical Association, 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - American Red Cross of Stanford University, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - American Sign language Club, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1987-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Amnesty International at Stanford, 1980-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Alpasa Conference, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Argentinos En Stanford, 1993-2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Armenian Students Association, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Art Department Graduate Students Association, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Artspan, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - ASHA-Stanford, 1993-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Asian American Health Initiative, 1992-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Asian American Theatre Project, 1978-2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Asian American graduate Student Assoc., 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Asian Pacific American Voices in Health, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Asia Pacific Entre, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Asian/Pacific Islander Heritage Month, 1988-2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Assoc. of Chinese Students and Scholars at Stanford, 1994-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - ASSU Course Guide, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - ASSU Speaker's Bureau, 1991-2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Atheist Freethinker Society, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Awash-Association of Women Academics in the Societal Sciences, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Baha'i Association at Stanford Sam, 1991-2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Ballet Folklorico de Stanford, 1979-2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Barrio Assistance Mentorship Program, 1987-2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Beat Junkies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Belgica, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Bent Spoon Student Dance Company, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Best Buddies, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - BioMASS, 1992-2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Bisexual, Gay, Lesbian Alliance Stanford (BGLAS), 1991-2002 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - SBSSA-Black Business Student Assn., 1983-2002 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Black and Queer at Stanford, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Black Graduate Students Association, 1988-2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Black Liberation Month Committee, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Black Pre-Law Society, 1976-2002 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Brazilian Students Association, 1979-2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - Blessed Abundance, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - Board Fellows, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - Bocce Ball Club of Stanford, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - Buddhist Community at Stanford, 1992-2003 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - Bursting the Bubble, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 53)
      - Business Association of Stanford Engineer'g Students, 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      - CAM-Integrative Medicine Interest Group, 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - Campus Girl Scouts of Stanford, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - Canadian Club of the GSB, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 57)
      - Cap and Gown, 1980-2002 (Box 1, Folder 58)
      - Capoeira Club, 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - Cardinal Ballet, 1994-2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
      - Cardinal Competitive Cheer, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - Cardinal Council Stanford Student-Athlete Advisory Group, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 62)
      - Caribbean Students Associations (CSA), 1990-2003 (Box 1, Folder 63)
      - CASE (Collective Artists for Social Expression), 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 64)
      - Catholic Community at Stanford-SAM, 1990-2003 (Box 1, Folder 65)
      - Central American Student Association at Stanford, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 66)
      - Chabab at Stanford, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 67)
      - Cherokee Student Group, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 68)
      - Chess Club of Stanford University, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 69)
      - Chi Alpha Christian Fellowship, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 70)
      - Chicano/Latino Big Sib/Lil Sib Program, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 71)
      - Chicano graduate Student Association, 1979-2003 (Box 1, Folder 72)
      - Chicanos in Health Education, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 73)
      - Chicano Latino Graduation Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 74)
      - ChinaRains, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 75)
      - Chinese Campus Evangelistic Fellowship, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 76)
      - Chinese Christian Fellowship at Stanford (SAM), 1990-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Christian Science Organization, 1978-2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Circle K International, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Stanford Class of 2004, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Coalition for Justice in Israel Palestine, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Colleges Against Cancer, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Colombian Students Association at Stanford University, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Community of Stanford Students with Disabilities, 1989-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - CORE-creation, Outreach, Respect, Education, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - College Ministries of Menlo Park: Cornerstone, 1991-2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Counterpoint, 1980-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Dance Preservation Society, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Decadence, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Democracy Matters, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Delta Gamma, 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Delta Gamma, 19951998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Derechos, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Dine', 1991-2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Double or Nothing, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Down with Gravity, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - East Palo Alto/Stanford Summer Academy, 1988-2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Educational Democracy for Youth, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)